Careful what you wish for.
Birth is a drama, mystery film directed by Jonathan Glazer.
It took Anna 10 years to recover from the death of her husband, Sean, but now she's on
the verge of marrying her boyfriend, Joseph, and finally moving on.
However, on the night of her engagement party, a young boy named Sean
turns up, saying he is her dead husband reincarnated.
At first she ignores the child, but his knowledge of her former husband's life is
uncanny, leading her to believe that he might be telling the truth.
Anna, played by Nicole Kidman.
Young Sean, played by Cameron Bright.
Joseph, played by Danny Huston.
Eleanor, played by Lauren Bacall.
Laura, played by Alison Elliott.
Bob, played by Arliss Howard.
Birth is a 2004 American psychological drama film
co-written and directed by Jonathan Glazer.
The film stars Nicole Kidman, Lauren Bacall, Cameron Bright, Danny Huston,
Arliss Howard, Peter Stormare, Ted Levine, and Anne Heche.
Its plot follows a woman who becomes convinced that her deceased
husband Sean is reincarnated as a ten-year-old boy.
Distributed by New Line Cinema, Birth premiered in competition at the 61st Venice International Film
Festival, polarizing critics upon its release and grossing $23.9 million on a budget of $20 million.
Kidman was nominated for a Golden Globe Award for Best Actress
in a Motion Picture – Drama for her performance.
The film explores themes of infidelity, new york city,
opera, loss of loved one, love letter.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.